Guide to the Carmel Bach Festival Tape Collection ARS.0025
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/23/1966; CBF082-CBF084; 4 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg Concerto no. 5, in D major, 07/23/1966; CBF082; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Di Tullio, Louise; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Waller, Rosemary; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981 (Reel CBF082)
  - The game of cards, 07/23/1966; CBF083; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano; Caldara, Antonio, 1670-1736; Hodges, Norma Jean; Armstrong, Karen, soprano; Burch, Carole, singer (Reel CBF083)
    Not in LC
  - Concerto for violin, K. 216, in G minor, 07/23/1966; CBF084; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Abel, David, violinist (Reel CBF084)
    Concertos, violin, orchestra, K. 216, G major.
  - Symphony no. 39, K. 543 in E flat major, 07/23/1966; CBF085; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF085)
    Symphonies, K. 543, E \u266D major
- The Mass in B minor, 07/24/1966; CBF086-CBF088; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Allen, Betty, 1930-; Bach Festival Chorus.; Law, Pauline; Brown, Melvin; Dunning, Edwin; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF086, Reel CBF088, Reel CBF087)
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/21/1967; CBF089-CBF090; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sacred Cantata No. 80, Ein' feste Burg ist unser Gott, 07/21/1967; CBF089; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Nason, Henry, tenor; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Gibson, Marie, singer; Love, Shirley; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale. (Reel CBF089)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Feste Burg ist unser Gott (Cantata)
  - Concerto in A minor for violin, 07/21/1967; CBF090; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Abel, David, violinist (Reel CBF090)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, violin, string orchestra, BWV 1041, A minor
  - Magnificat, 07/21/1967; CBF090a; Glover, Robert, tenor; Festival Chorale.; Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Stevenson, Delcina; Oliver, Robert, singer; Love, Shirley
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/22/1967; CBF091-CBF094; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Concerto for D-Trumpet, two oboes and continuo, 07/22/1967; CBF091; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Stevens, Jean; Haug, Edward (Reel CBF091)
    Uniform Title
    Concertos, trumpet, oboes (2), string orchestra, TWV 53:D2, D major
    Concertos (Oboes (2), trumpet with string orchestra)
  - Concerto in C major for piccolo, F. VI, no.4, 07/22/1967; CBF091; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Di Tullio, Louise; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF091)
  - Sacred cantata no. 82, Ich habe genug, 07/22/1967; CBF092; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Paul, Thomas, 1934- (Reel CBF092)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich habe genug
  - Symphony no. 41, K.551, Jupiter, 07/22/1967; CBF094; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF094)
- The passion of our Lord according to St. John, 07/23/1967; CBF095-CBF097; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Thomas, Paul, singer; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Gibson, Marie, singer; Love, Shirley; Nason, Henry, tenor; Remsberg, Bruce (Reel CBF097, Reel CBF096, Reel CBF095)
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Johannespassion
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/24/1967; CBF098-099; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.4, 07/24/1967; CBF098; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Goldsmith, Kenneth, 1938-; Gruskin, Shelley, 1936-; Salgo, Sandor; Davenport, LaNoue, 1922-1999; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF098)
  - Concerto for two pianos, K.365, 07/24/1967; CBF099; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Salkind, Peggy; Salkind, Milton (Reel CBF099)
    Concertos, pianos (2), orchestra, K. 365, E\u266D major
    Concertos (Pianos (2))
  - Sacred Cantata no. 106, Gottes Zeit ist die allerbeste Zeit., 07/24/1967; CBF098; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Davenport, LaNoue, 1922-1999; Tede, Margery, 1940-; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Oliver, Robert, singer; Festival Chorale.; Davidoff, Judith; Gruskin, Shelley, 1936-; Fulkerson, Jean; Nason, Henry, tenor; Kell, Sally (Reel CBF098)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Gottes Zeit ist die allerbeste Zeit. In deine H\u00C4nde
- Concert, 07/25/1967; CBF100-CBF101; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Suite no.3, in D major, 07/25/1967; CBF100; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Salgo, Sandor; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF100)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1068, D major.
    Suites (Chamber orchestra)
  - Concerto for viola da gamba, in D major, 07/25/1967; CBF100; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Boismortier, Joseph Bodin de, 1689-1755 (Reel CBF100)
    Concertos, violoncello, string orchestra, op. 26, D major
  - Judicum Salomonis. Oratorio, 07/25/1967; CBF100; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Carissimi, Giacomo, 1605-1674; Gibson, Marie, singer; Robinson, Richard, singer; Salgo, Sandor; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano; Oliver, Robert, singer (Reel CBF100)
    Judicium Salomonis
  - Symphony no.102 in B flat, 07/25/1967; CBF101; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Salgo, Sandor (Reel CBF101)
    Symphonies, H. I, 102, B♭ major
- Recital, Parish Hall, All Saints Episcopal Church, 07/25/1967; CBF102-104; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Cantata, Hemmet den Eifer, Verbannet die Rache, 07/25/1967; CBF102; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Linsley, Ralph; Davidoff, Judith; Davenport, LaNoue, 1922-1999; Schonbrun, Sheila; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Salkind, Milton; Salkind, Peggy (Reel CBF102)
    Harmonischer Gottes-Dienst. Hemmet den Eifer
    Solo cantatas, Secular
  - The Blessed Virgin's Expostulation, 07/25/1967; CBF103; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Schonbrun, Sheila; Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695; Linsley, Ralph; Davidoff, Judith (Reel CBF103)
    Tell me, some pitying angel
    Songs (High voice) with continuo
  - Sonata no.3, in F major, for piano, four hands, 07/25/1967; CBF103; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Salkind, Milton; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Salkind, Peggy (Reel CBF103)
    Sonatas, piano, 4 hands, K. 497, F major
    Sonatas (Piano, 4 hands)
- Messa concertata, 07/26/1967; CBF105-CBF106; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Cavalli, Pier Francesco, 1602-1676; Glover, Robert, tenor; Howe, Francesca; Tede, Margery, 1940-; Love, Shirley; Stevenson, Delcina; Salgo, Sandor; Remsberg, Bruce; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Nason, Henry, tenor (Reel CBF105, Reel CBF106)
  Musiche sacre. Messa
- Saul, 07/27/1967; CBF107-CBF109; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Cariaga, Marvellee, singer; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Howe, Francesca; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Nason, Henry, tenor; Oliver, Robert, singer; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Salgo, Sandor (Reel CBF107, Reel CBF108, Reel CBF109)
  Saul
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/28/1967; CBF110-CBF112; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sacred Cantata no. 80, Ein' feste Burg ist unser Gott, 07/28/1967; CBF110; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Love, Shirley; Nason, Henry, tenor; Paul, Thomas, 1934- (Reel CBF110)
  - Concerto in A minor for violin, 07/28/1967; CBF111; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Abel, David, violinist (Reel CBF111)
  - Magnificat, 07/28/1967; CBF112; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788; Love, Shirley; Glover, Robert, tenor; Stevenson, Delcina; Oliver, Robert, singer; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus. (Reel CBF111)
    Magnificat, H. 772, D major
- Recital, Parish Hall, All Saints Episcopal Church, 07/28/1967; CBF113-CBF116; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Spiritual Concerto, Wie der Hirsch schreyet, 07/28/1967; CBF113; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Pohle, David, 1624-1695; Salgo, Sandor; Love, Shirley; Hull, James, singer; Haug, Edward (Reel CBF113)
    Wie der Hirsch schreyet
    Solo cantatas, Sacred (High voice)
  - Cantata, The morning, 07/28/1967; CBF113; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Arne, Thomas Augustine, 1710-1778 (Reel CBF113)
    Cantatas (1755). Morning
    Solo cantatas, Secular (High voice)
  - Concerto for baroque trumpet, 07/28/1967; CBF114; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Torelli, Giuseppe, 1658-1709; Haug, Edward (Reel CBF114)
    Concertos, trumpet, string orchestra, D major
    Concertos (Trumpet)
  - Cantata, Ah del celebre confin, 07/28/1967; CBF115; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Pradas Gall\u00C9n, Jos\u00C9, 1689-1757; Love, Shirley (Reel CBF115)
    Ah! Del c\u00C9lebre conf\u00CDn
    Solo cantatas, Sacred (Medium voice)
  - Duets for two tenors. Il mio core e un mar di pianti; Vaghi rai, pupille ardenti, 07/28/1967; CBF116; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Hull, James, singer; Carissimi, Giacomo, 1605-1674; Schwabacher, James, Jr. (Reel CBF116)
    Mio core \u00C9 un mar di pianti
    Cantatas, Secular; Vocal duets with continuo
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/29/1967; CBF117-CBF119; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Concerto for D trumpet, two oboes and contimuo, 07/29/1967; CBF117; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Stevens, Jean; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Haug, Edward; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF117)
    Concertos (Oboes (2), trumpet with continuo)
  - Sacred cantata no.82, Ich habe genug, 07/29/1967; CBF117; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Paul, Thomas, 1934- (Reel CBF117)
  - Concerto in C major for piccolo, F. VI, no.4, 07/29/1967; CBF118; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Di Tullio, Louise; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Bach Festival Chorus. (Reel CBF118)
    Concertos, recorder, string orchestra, RV 443, C major
  - Symphony no.41 K.551, Jupiter, 07/29/1967; CBF119; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF119)
    Symphonies, K. 551, C major
- Recital, Parish Hall, All Saints Episcopal Church, 07/29/1967; CBF120-CBF122; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sonata no.3, in C major, for solo violin senza basso, 07/29/1967; CBF120; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Abel, David, violinist; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF120)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Sonata, no. 3
  - Partita no.3, in E major, for solo violin senza basso, 07/29/1967; CBF122; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF122)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 3
    Suites (Violin)
  - Aria, Seufzer, Traenen, from cantata 21; aria, Was Gott tut, ist wohl getan, from cantata 100, 07/29/1967; CBF121; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Skolnick, Paula; Wachsmuth, Sherry; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Ahrens, Kenneth, organist; Power, Margot; Dust\u00E9, Raymond (Reel CBF121)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich hatte viel Bek\u00DC̈mmernis. Seufzer, Tr\u00C4̈nen, Kummer, Not; Was Gott tut, das ist wohlgetan (Cantata), BWV 100
    Cantatas, Sacred--Excerpts
  - Partita no.3, in E major, for solo violin senza basso, 07/29/1967; CBF122; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Abel, David, violinist (Reel CBF122)
- The passion of our Lord according to St. John, 07/30/1967; CBF123-CBF125; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Utterback, Lois; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Brightbill, Franz; Bernard, Robert, singer; Oliver, Robert, singer; Festival Chorale.; Robinson, Richard, singer; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Bach Festival Chorus. (Reel CBF124, Reel CBF125, Reel CBF123)
- Works of Johann Sebastian and Johann Christoph Bach, 07/18/1969; CBF126-CBF127; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Overture no.2, BWV 1067, in B minor, 07/18/1969; CBF126; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Di Tullio, Louise (Reel CBF126)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1067, B minor
    Overtures
  - Sacred Cantata, BWV 56, Ich will den Kreuzstab gerne tragen, 07/18/1969; CBF127a; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Festival Chorale.; Paul, Thomas, 1934-
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich will den Kreuzstab gerne tragen
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.6, in B flat major, 07/18/1969; CBF127; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Trampler, Walter; Adams, Ruth, viola da gamba player; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Davidoff, Judith; De Keyser, Joanna; Goldsmith, Pamela, violist; Mitchell, Lucien, violist (Reel CBF127)
  - Cantata, Es erhub sich ein Streit, 07/18/1969; CBF127; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Jarvis, Larry; Gibson, Marie, singer; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Clark, Richard J., 1943-; Burch, Carole, singer; Bach, Johann Christian, 1735-1782 (Reel CBF127)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Es erhub sich ein Streit
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/19/1969; CBF128-CBF129; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Passacaille (1695), 07/19/1969; CBF128a; Le Sage de Rich\u00C9e, Philipp Franz; Dust\u00E9, Raymond
    Cabinet der Lauten. Passacaglia \u00C0 discretion
    Passacaglias (Lute)
  - Aria, Cara sposa, 07/19/1969; CBF128a; Simon, Joanna, 1940-; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759
    Rinaldo. Cara sposa
  - Aria, Che far\u00F2 senza Euridice, 07/19/1969; CBF128a; Simon, Joanna, 1940-; Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787
    Orfeo ed Euridice. Che far\u00F2 senza Euridice
  - Symphony no.102, in B flat major, 07/19/1969; CBF128; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF128)
    Symphonies, H. I, 102, B\u266D major
  - Sinfonia Concertante, K.-E 320d, for violin and viola, 07/19/1969; CBF129; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Trampler, Walter; Shapiro, Eudice; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF129)
    Sinfonia concertante, violin, viola & orchestra, K. 320d (364) E\u266D major.
- The passion according to St. Matthew, 07/20/1969; CBF130-CBF132; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Goeke, Leo; Grimes, Bruce; Festival Chorale.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Clark, Richard J., 1943-; Cole, Charles, singer; Bernard, Robert, singer; Whitsitt, Don; Cabral, Herbert; Simon, Joanna, 1940-; Bach Festival Chorus.; Waterbury, Robert, singer; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Masuko, Tsutomu; Murray, David, baritone; Hinshaw, Sue; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942- (Reel CBF130, Reel CBF132, Reel CBF131)
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matth\u00E4̈uspassion
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/21/1969; CBF133-135; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg concert no.1, BWV 1046, in F major, 07/21/1969; CBF133; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Stevens, Jean; Dickow, Robert; Biondi, Eleanor, oboist; Goldsmith, Kenneth, 1938-; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Mazenko, Max; Griffin, Morgan, bassoonist (Reel CBF133)
  - Concerto for violin, K. 219, in A major, 07/21/1969; CBF134; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Shapiro, Eudice; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF134)
    Concertos, violin, orchestra, K. 219, A major
  - Sacred cantata, Lass, F\u00FCrstin, lass noch einen Strahl. Trauer -Ode BWV 198, 07/21/1969; CBF135; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Davidoff, Judith; Goeke, Leo; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Springfels, Mary; Simon, Joanna, 1940-; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Williams, Christopher, lute player (Reel CBF135)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Lass, F\u00FC̈rstin, lass noch einen Strahl
- The fairy queen, 07/22/1969; CBF136-CBF138; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Chappell, Gertrude; Mahroom, Roxanne; Clark, Richard J., 1943-; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Powell, Marilyn; Clark, Suzanne, musician; Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695; Conrad, Arthur; Gibson, Marie, singer; Bales, Suzanne; Graves, Jon; Bogard, Carole; Jarvis, Larry; Burch, Carole, singer; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Salgo, Sandor; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Simon, Joanna, 1940- (Reel CBF136, Reel CBF137, Reel CBF138)
  Fairy queen
  Masques with music
- Bach and Beethoven, 07/17/1970; CBF139-CBF140; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Cantata, BWV 71, Gott ist mein K\u00F6nig, 07/17/1970; 139a; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale.; McCoy, Seth; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Bach Festival Chorus.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Gott ist mein K\u00F6̈nig
  - Concerto for Harpsichord, BWV 1052, in D minor, 07/17/1970; CBF139; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Valenti, Fernando (Reel CBF139)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichord, string orchestra, BWV 1052, D minor
  - Concerto for violin, BWV 1042, in E major, 07/17/1970; CBF139a; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Monosoff, Sonya
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, violin, string orchestra, BWV 1042, E major
  - Fantasy for piano, chorus and orchestra, op.80, 07/17/1970; CBF140; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Graudan, Joanna; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus. (Reel CBF140)
    Fantasien, piano, mixed voices, orchestra, op. 80, C minor
    Piano with orchestra; Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- Homage to the Baroque, 07/18/1970; CBF141-CBF143; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Le tombeau de Couperin, 07/18/1970; CBF141; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF141)
    Tombeau de Couperin
  - Motet, O Heiland, reiss die Himmel auf, 07/18/1970; CBF141; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897 (Reel CBF141)
    Motets, mixed voices, op. 74. O Heiland, reiss die Himmel auf
    Part songs, Sacred; Motets
  - Suite de Pulcinella, 07/18/1970; CBF142; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Zeyen, Mary Louise; Waller, Rosemary; Andrews, Richard T., double bass player; Freifeld, Bruce, violinist; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Hall, Thomas (Reel CBF142)
    Pulcinella. Suite
  - Concerto for piano, violin and cello, op.56, in C major, 07/18/1970; CBF143; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Silberstein, Jascha; Graudan, Joanna; Monosoff, Sonya; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 (Reel CBF143)
    Concertos, piano trio, orchestra, op. 56, C major
    Concertos (Piano trio with string orchestra)
- The mass in B minor, 07/19/1970; CBF144-CBF147; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Law, Pauline; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Bach Festival Orchestra.; McCoy, Seth; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano (Reel CBF144, Reel CBF147, Reel CBF145)
- Bach and Mozart, 07/20/1970; CBF148-CBF151; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg concerto no.4, BWV 1049, in G major, 07/20/1970; CBF148; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Ballinger, Peter; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Haynes, Bruce, 1942-; Waller, Rosemary (Reel CBF148)
  - Concerto for flute and harp, K.299, in C major, 07/20/1970; CBF149; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Peck, Donald; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Adams, Anne, harpist (Reel CBF149)
    Concertos, flute, harp, orchestra, K. 299, C major
  - Cantata, BWV 8, Liebster Gott, wann werd ich sterben?, 07/20/1970; CBF150; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Law, Pauline; Festival Chorale.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Pracht, Mary Ellen; McCoy, Seth (Reel CBF150)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Liebster Gott, wenn werd ich sterben
  - Symphony no.39, K.543, in E flat major, 07/20/1970; CBF151; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF151)
    Symphonies, K. 543, E\u00F6 major
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/21/1970; CBF152-CBF155; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Cantata, BWV, 53, Schlage doch, gew\u00FCnschte Stunde, 07/21/1970; CBF152; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Law, Pauline; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF152)
    Hoffmann, Melchior, ca. 1685-1715. Schlage doch, gew\u00FCnschte Stunde
  - Sonata W.132, in A minor, for solo flute, 07/21/1970; CBF152; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788; Peck, Donald (Reel CBF152)
    Sonatas, flute, H. 562, A minor
    Sonatas (Flute)
  - Songs of David. Mein Herz ist bereit, 07/21/1970; CBF153; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Buxtehude, Dietrich, 1637-1707; Paul, Thomas, 1934-
    Mein Herz ist bereit
  - Fili mi Absalon, 07/21/1970; CBF153a; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Sch\u00FCtz,, Heinrich,, 1585-1672.
    Symphoniae sacrae, 1 pars. Fili mi, Absalon
  - The camerata musicale, 07/21/1970; CBF154-CBF155; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Wood, Patricia Davenport; Baldwin, John, d. 1615; Cornysh, Robert, 1465-1523; Dufay, Guillaume, d. 1474; Fuenllana, Miguel de, 16th cent.; Marcus, Shirley; Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603?; Adams, Ruth, viola da gamba player; Rutherford, William W.; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767 (Reel CBF155, Reel CBF154)
    Instrumental music
- Music from the golden age of Spain and missions in the New World, 07/22/1970; CBF156-CBF157; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - O crux, ave, spes unica, 07/22/1970; CBF156; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Morales, Crist\u00F3bal de, ca. 1500-1553. (Reel CBF156)
    O crux, ave, spes unica
  - Lauda Sion salvatorem, 07/22/1970; CBF156; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Garcia Nunes, Jos\u00E9 Maur\u00EDcio, 1767-1830; Elias, Daniel; Kimmel, Natasha; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Cummings, Claudia (Reel CBF156)
    Psalms (Music); Part songs, Sacred; Motets
  - Concerto no.4, in G major, for organ and harpsichord, 07/22/1970; CBF156; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Linsley, Ralph; Ahrens, Kenneth, organist; Soler, Antonio, 1729-1783 (Reel CBF156)
    Concertos, organs (2). No. 4; arr.
    Concertos (Harpsichord and organ with chamber orchestra)
  - Guineo a 5, 07/22/1970; CBF156; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; DeWeese, Glenna, singer; Brightbill, Alvin J.; Utterback, Lois; Fernandes, Gaspar, d. 1629; Armstead, Robert P., bass; Bales, Suzanne (Reel CBF156)
    Villancicos (Music)
  - Laudate pueri, a 4, 07/22/1970; CBF156; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bellows, Beverly; Dur\u00E1n de la Motta, Antonio (Reel CBF156)
  - Versos al organo, con duo para chirimias, 07/22/1970; CBF157; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Olaeta, Camille; Willoughby, Susan; Blasco de Nebra, Manuel, ca. 1750-1784; Bubb, Charles, trumpet player (Reel CBF157)
  - Luzid fragrante Rosa, 07/22/1970; CBF157; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Nelson, Nelda; Quiroz,, Manuel Jos\u00E9 de,, d. 1765; Ahrens, Kenneth, organist (Reel CBF157)
  - Kyrie and Gloria, from mass, 07/22/1970; CBF157; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Gorham, Margaret; Zajac, Joan; Goleeke, Tom; Zipoli, Domenico, 1688-1726 (Reel CBF157)
    Misa a San Ignacio
    Kyrie eleison (Music); Gloria in excelsis Deo (Music); Masses--Excerpts